the smart fit mine asked me
man I always see you around here
but i never see you training as soon as she knows
look
this bank here man
Choose here or pet service
on Instagram to be able to promote my work
service is not remembered right uncle
if you don't create this opportunity
no one will create for you
boom that's it bro
bora work
let's go let's go boss
I'm cleaning the window here
barbershop guy
raised a demand for me to walk a dog
and i will do this
haha
hello tamo together valeu
and there you go bro
it's 1 hour barbershop or downtown
I'll give you 1 job
so you can have more customers
visualization
then I help you even in this design
then I'll give you 1 morale
I can give you 1 quick treat
this moral
it's up
the trick there bro is us
love 1 more uncle
are beautiful
that's it bro
will seize this opportunity
while your brother
my business
I go here earning my money
knows face
sometimes we get a lot ego from
i need one thing
I have an idea
but you have to leave point a to go to point b
it's on hand
so have it in your head
march in progress
day eight
tamo together
thank you saw
sit here
I was in the barbershop now bro
and then I started repairing the hall bro
i think this barber niche
beauty salon
is a whore of a power to be exploited
everyone goes after beauty
aesthetics
cut the hair
does things knows
I have some idea for this
but then I'm going to search a little stop here
if you give a certain hand
it's half the way
until tomorrow
When Will